{
  "difficultquestions": [
    {
      "question": "Total constructor string class have?",
      "answer1": "A)13",
      "answer2": "B)3",
      "answer3": "C)7",
      "answer4": "D)20",
      "correct": "A)13"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the return type of a method that does not return any value.",
      "answer1": "A)int",
      "answer2": "B)void",
      "answer3": "C)double",
      "answer4": "D)none",
      "correct": "B)void"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where does the system stores parameters and local variables a method is invoked?",
      "answer1": "A)Heap",
      "answer2": "B)Array",
      "answer3": "C)Stack",
      "answer4": "D)Tree",
      "correct": "C)Stack"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the modifier which cannot be used for constructor.",
      "answer1": "A)public",
      "answer2": "B)protected",
      "answer3": "C)private",
      "answer4": "D)static",
      "correct": "D)static"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the variable declared in a class for the use of all methods of the class called?",
      "answer1": "A)Instance variables",
      "answer2": "B)Reference variable",
      "answer3": "C)Object",
      "answer4": "D)None",
      "correct": "A)Instance Variables"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the implicit return type of constructor?",
      "answer1": "A)No return type",
      "answer2": "B)A class object in which it is defined",
      "answer3": "C)void",
      "answer4": "D)None",
      "correct": "B)A class in which it is defined"
    },
    {
      "question": "When is the finalize() method called?",
      "answer1": "A)Before a variable goes out of scope",
      "answer2": "B)Before an object goes out of scope",
      "answer3": "C)Before garbage collection",
      "answer4": "D)None",
      "correct": "C)Before garbage collection"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the prototype of the default constructor.\n public clas  Solution{}",
      "answer1": "A)Solution(void)",
      "answer2": "B)Solution()",
      "answer3": "C)public Solution(void)",
      "answer4": "D)public Solution()",
      "correct": "D)public Solution()"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the correct way of declaring constructor.\n public class Solution{}",
      "answer1": "A)Solution(){}",
      "answer2": "B)public Solution(){}",
      "answer3": "C)Both (A) and (B)",
      "answer4": "D)None",
      "correct": "C)Both (A) and (B)"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Runnable?",
      "answer1": "A)Abstract class",
      "answer2": "B)Class",
      "answer3": "C)Method",
      "answer4": "D)Interface",
      "correct": "D)Interface"
    }
  ]
}